export const questions = [
    {
        question: 'Around __ trees are cut down each day.',
        a: 13000,
        b: 24000,
        c: 25000,
        d: 27000,
        correct: "d"

    },

    {
        question: 'what is the answer????????',
        a: "aajssf;a",
        b: "bjsdlf",
        c: "csddfsf",
        d: "dsdfdsf",
        correct: "c"
    },

    {
        question: 'whats sarahs last name',
        a: "hong",
        b: "ha",
        c: "hu",
        d: "hoo",
        correct: "a"
    },


    {
        question: 'What percentage of global freshwater is used by agriculture?',
        a: "50",
        b: "70",
        c: "30",
        d: "90",
        correct: "b"
    },

    {
        question: 'Which greenhouse gas emissions are primarily associated with burning fossil fuels?',
        a: "Carbon Monoxide",
        b: "Methane",
        c: "Carbon Dioxide",
        d: "Nitrous Oxide",
        correct: "c"
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the concentration of carbon dioxide (CO2) in the atmosphere as of 2018?',
        a: "300 parts per million",
        b: "350 parts per million",
        c: "408 parts per million",
        d: "500 parts per million",
        correct: "c"
    },

    {
        question: 'Which technology is known for turning smog into jewelry?',
        a: "Smog-Free Project",
        b: "Carbon Neutral Cities Alliance",
        c: "Ozone Layer Healing Initiative",
        d: "EDF and Google Earth Outreach",
        correct: "a"
    },

    {
        question: 'How much energy can be saved by recycling one aluminum can?',
        a: "Enough to run a TV for 1 hour",
        b: "Enough to run a TV for 2 hours",
        c: "Enough to run a TV for 3 hours",
        d: "Enough to run a TV for 4 hours",
        correct: "c"
    },


    {
        question: 'What percentage of global biodiversity is protected by the worlds indigenous population?',
        a: "70",
        b: "60",
        c: "80",
        d: "50",
        correct: "c"
    },

    {
        question: 'How much of the worlds total oxygen is produced in the Amazon rainforest?',
        a: "10",
        b: "20",
        c: "30",
        d: "50",
        correct: "b"
    },


    {
        question: 'Who famously sailed to North America from Sweden instead of flying for climate activism?',
        a: "Jane Fonda",
        b: "Greta Thunberg",
        c: "Leonardo DiCaprio",
        d: "Prince Harry",
        correct: "b"
    }

]